Hi!
Now what to wear with this dress.
As you can see.
I've chosen a necklace here.
There is more than one thing wrong with this choice I've made; the major part of this necklace has a print and my dress has a print.
These two prints do not work well together.
I mean I have busy print here filled with navy blues, green s and just really beautiful color and then I have this charm, it's kind of blah.
It doesn't mix well with what I am wearing.
Second of all the length of this necklace is not the length that you would be really shooting for, for a neckline like this.
It is hitting somewhere right in the middle.
It's not quite long enough and not quite short enough.
If I was somewhere around this length, the length would at least be complimentary but again, this charm just throws the entire outfit off.
So we would not want to choose this necklace with this particular outfit.l